http://www.kart.org/privacy

Privacy Policy
The privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") of KART is intended to explain how and why we collect information, and protect the privacy of visitors to this website. KART reserves the right, without prior notice, to change the terms of our Privacy Policy effective immediately upon the posting of said changes.
IP ADDRESSES AND COOKIES
To evaluate the experience of visitors to the website, identify and correct technical problems with the server, make note of trends in website usage and generally improve the quality of www.kart.org, we collect an IP address from all website visitors. The IP address is a number automatically assigned to your computer when you access the Internet. IP addresses do not provide personally identifiable information.
KART’s website may use "cookies" - pieces of information transferred between your computer and a website intended to make the browsing experience easier. Cookies keep track of website-specific passwords or personal preference settings so you are not required to input this information each time you visit a website. Most browsers are configured to accept cookies by default. However, you can manually deactivate this feature, usually by accessing the controls or preferences menus within your browser software. Consult the "help" features of your web browser for more information.
LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES
KART's website contains links to other websites containing relevant information and resources. We make every effort to ensure that off-site links lead to accurate, responsibly used information. However, KART is not responsible for the content or online policies of other websites and online resources (including downloads). Using any link that directs you away from www.kart.org means that you are entering a new website with its own policies and privacy statements.
About
Contact
News
Join Kart
© 2020 KART. All rights reserved. Privacy Policy
